Today we are going to make smothered chicken with maque choux casserole.
So now we are going to prepare the chicken but here is how we are going to do it.
We want to create a flour dredge for it to brown up nicely.
So here is how we do that.
So I just like to pour some flour.
I have a paper plate here you can use whatever you need then put that in here.
We have a wheat flour here, you can just use regular white flour if you like pretty southern tradition to do.
Seasoning it up a little bit so I'm going to use some black pepper, be pretty liberal with this because it is in the flour so all this is not going to be on the chicken.
You have that and you have some nice salt here to put in.
This is going to be a coating seasoning for your chicken.